大家好
ROB DODSON: Hey, everyone.
今天在播客上我们要回顾一下
Today on the podcast, we're going to be taking a look back
以前的core页面例子
at our old core pages example.
我们要修正一下它 让它使用新的iron页面
We're going to revise it so it uses the new iron pages
元素
element.
我们来看看吧
Let's check it out.
好的 这是我们今天要做的东西
OK, so this is what we're going to be building today.
这是一个猫录（catalogue本意为目录）
It is a cat-alogue.
现在知道了吗
Get it?
对啦
Yeah.
它基本上有点像一个小小的图像传送带
And it's basically kind of like a little image carousel.
所以你能看到它有这些下一张和上一张的选项
So you can see it's got these Next and Previous buttons.
我点击它们的时候 就会循环播放不同的猫咪
As I click on them, it cycles through different photos
图片
of cats.
而且你能看见这里有文本区域
And you can see here that there is this text field right here
当我修改上面的索引时 它也会
and, as I change that index, it is also
更新我们正在看的猫咪图片
updating which cat photo we are currently looking at.
为了建立这套东西
And so to build this whole thing,
我们要用新的iron页面元素
we're going to use the new iron pages element.
现在 你看我们的索引文件的源
Now, looking at our source for our index file here,
你可以看见我的网页元素
you can see that I've already got my web components
多项填充已经就位
polyfills in place.
我已经引入了我的猫录元素
I've already gone ahead and imported my cat-alogue element,
而且已经将它放在页面里了 就在这儿
and I've actually dropped it into the page here as well.
那么我们差不多准备好了
So we're pretty much already set up to go.
现在 我想指出的是
Now, thing that I want to point out
我将图像目录放在这儿
is that I've got this images directory over here,
而在那里面有几张猫咪的照片
and, inside of there, I've just got a few photos of some cats.
这些照片照的是一名Polymer Eng团队成员的
These are taken from a member of the Polymer Eng team's
猫科动物朋友 我们现在当范例
own feline friend here that we're
用一下 这还蛮酷的
using for our example, which is pretty cool.
现在 在猫录元素定义中
Now, in the cat-alogue element definition,
你可以看见这像一个挺典型的Polymer
you can see that this looks like a pretty typical Polymer
元素
element.
在上面 我们在引入Polymer HTML
At the top, we are importing Polymer HTML
来确保依赖性被载入以备我们使用
to make sure that dependency is loaded and ready for us.
那个有一个猫录的编码
That one has an ID of cat-alogue,
跟Polymer构造器
which matches the is property that we have down here
下面的属性相匹配
in the Polymer constructor.
我要做的第一件事是
And the first thing that I'm going to do
给我们的元素添加样式以使主元素具有样式
is just add a style to our element to style the host.
那么我们在使标签本身具有样式 我将它
So we're styling the tag itself, and I'm
发送到显示模块
sending it to display block.
我谨慎的处理这儿的很多元素
And I typically do this for many of my elements,
只是因为 根据默认 定制元素是内联显示的
just because, by default, custom elements are displayed inline,
而我通常觉得它们要么是模块 要么是内联模块
and usually I want things to be either block or inline block.
所以我经常第一步就做这个以完全避免任何样式上的
So I always do this first to avoid any style weirdness
差错
down the line.
现在 那个已经就位 我要往下进行
Now, with that in place, I'm ready to go ahead and just
引入iron页面了
import iron pages.
我已经用Bower安装了它
I've already installed it using Bower.
所以我只用将它从Bower元素目录中
So I'm just going to pull it out of the Bower components
提出来并放在我这里的元素里
directory and drop it into my element here.
之后我就可以用这个方便的iron页面片段点击出
Then I can use this handy iron pages snippet to spit out
一些iron页面样板
some iron pages boilerplate.
顺便说一下 这个片段是我的片段包的一部分
This snippet, by the way, is part of my snippets package.
所以我有Sublime的片段 从这儿可以看到
So I've got snippets for both Sublime, which you can get over
你也可以看到  还有Atom的片段
here, and snippets for Atom, which you get over here.
它们相当相当有用 而且它们都设定好了
They are really, really useful, and they are set up
可以支持iron元素和纸张元素
to support the iron elements and the paper elements,
所以它使写这样的代码变得容易一点了
so it makes it a little bit easier to write code like this.
而且你可以在这看见iron页面
And you'll see here that iron pages
很像老的core页面元素
looks a lot like the old core pages element.
它有一个被选择的属性 这
It has a selected attribute, and this
决定了哪一个选项
defines which of these sections will
在某一时刻显示出来
be displaying at any one point.
现在 默认为零
Right now, it's just defaulting to 0,
所以它会是这里的第一个选项
so it'll be this first section here,
我要在这东西上再加一点内容
and I'm going to add a little bit of content to this thing.
我要放几个图像标签进来
I'm just going to drop in some image tags,
这些可以链接我们的猫咪照片
and these are going to link up to our cat photos.
而且我为了可供访问给它们设定了所有的Alt属性
And I've given them all Alt attributes for accessibility,
而且我想把它们所有都明确地设定一个375像素的
and I also want to give them all an explicit height of 375
高度
pixels.
所以我要给它们一个pic类
So I'm going to give them a pic class,
那样我就可以使它们具有样式
just so I can style them.
之后我要给它们设定高度
And then I'm just going to give them a height,
只是为了展示方便
just for the sake of this demo, so
那样我们就不用看着有差错的
that we don't have images that are
都是不同尺寸的图像了
all wonky and different sizes.
那么现在我们其实可以预览这个东西了
So now we can actually preview this thing.
因为iron页面被设定为显示它的第一个选项
And because iron pages is set to display its first section
元素 我们的第一张猫咪照片
element, we get our very first cat photo
出现在屏幕上 真是顶呱呱啊
showing up on screen, which is pretty rad.
现在 我想做的下一件事是
Now, the next thing I want to do is
创建可以让我在不同猫咪照片中
create those buttons that let me toggle back and forth
向前向后切换的按钮
between different cat photos.
为了达到目的 我要在我的iron下面创建一个div
So to do that, I'm going to create a div underneath my iron
页面 我就打算命名为controls
pages, and I'm just going to call it controls.
还有 在这里面 我就放置
And, inside of here, I'll just drop in
几个普通的 平常的 老的HTML按钮
a couple of vanilla, just regular, old HTML buttons.
但是有一点不同的是
But the one thing that's different
我要给它们设一些声明式事件绑定
is that I'm going to give them some of these declarative event
或者我应该说事件处理程序
event bindings or event handlers, I should say.
这些是很有用的
So these are really useful.
这些是Polymer为你添加的特性
These are features that Polymer adds for you
好设定事件接听项
to set up event listeners.
这些东西的好处是它们不只设置好
The nice thing about these is that not only do they set up
事件接听项 而且还在元素被从Dom取出时
the event listener, but they handle removing the event
移除事件接听项
listener when the element is taken out
这对于预防像内存泄漏的事
of the Dom, which is really handy for preventing things
是非常有用的
like memory leaks.
那么现在我不知道
So right now I don't know what I'm
怎样运用 但是
going to do with these methods, but I'm
我会继续 差不多在我的原型里将它们
going to go ahead and just sort of stub them out
连接起来
in my prototype.
所以我要继续预留出
So I'll go ahead and I'll stub out
转到上一页和转到下一页
Go Previous as well as Go Next.
还有我之所以不知道该对这些怎么办
And the reason why I don't know what I'm going to do with these
是因为我还没有
is because I haven't
深入钻研iron页面的
really dug into the Docs for iron pages
所以我真的不知道怎么告诉它继续或者后退
So I don't really know how to tell it to go next or back.
为了能做那个 我们要跳到元素目录
To do that, we will hop over to the elements catalog
element.polymer-project.org 然后找到iron元素
at elements.polymer-project.org and scope out the iron elements
再将页面拉下来直到找到iron页面
and kind of scroll down the page until we find iron pages,
就在这底下呢
which is right down here at the bottom.
我把它放大一点
And I'll boost this up a little bit,
你们就可以更清楚地看到这个页面了
just so you can kind of see this page a bit better
这儿有几件我得
because there's a couple things that I really
指出来的事
want to point out.
第一件是这个源按钮
The first is this source button.
这个其实是我们最近才
So this is something that we just recently
添加到目录的
added to the catalog.
它的功能是 顾名思义
And what this does is, as the name implies,
可以让你真的去到GitHub
it allows you to go to the actual GitHub
repo找你感兴趣的元素
repo for the element that you are interested in.
所以你可以去到这 还有 如果你想提交一个问题
So you can go here and, if you want to file an issue,
就在这儿点击提交
this is the place to do it.
你可以点击元素源 你到它的repo
So you go to the element source, you go to its repo,
并专门向那个标签提交问题
and you file an issue specifically to that tag.
另一件你需要做的是
And then the other thing you can do here,
很明显 是阅读那个元素的源
obviously, is go and read the source for the element.
当你在深入学习一个元素的时候
And this is super handy when you're
这可是超级方便
trying to learn like what's going on inside of an element.
另一件我想指出的事是
The other thing that I want to point out
也许有些人易忽略这底下的
that maybe some folks miss is this little behaviors panel
行为面板
down here.
那么现在你看着iron页面
So right now you're looking at iron pages,
然后你可以看见有这个属性显示
and you can see that it's got this one property that it says
它能定义 但是实际上我们
that it defines, but actually, we
知道这下面有两个行为在运行
know that there are these two behaviors down here that it's
即意味着 如果你能回想起
implementing, which means, if you recall from one
前面一集我们讨论过行为的话
of our previous episodes where we discussed behaviors,
我们知道这实际上混合了附加的属性
we know that it's actually mixing in additional properties
和方法 而这些我们可以使用
and methods that we should have access to.
那么如果我们到下面点击iron Selectable Behavior
So if we go down and click on the iron Selectable Behavior,
我们能看到有几个是元素
we can see that there are several properties that
的属性 实际上我们
are element implements, and in fact, we've
在这下面也有一些方法
got some methods down here as well.
那么我们有一个方法 可以选择特定值
So we've got methods for selecting a specific value,
可以选择下一页和前一页之类的
selecting Next and selecting Previous, et cetera.
所以那就是我要
So that's actually what I'm going
在我连接起来的那些方法中使用的
to use in those stubbed out methods that I created.
我要用这些选择下一页和前一页的方法
I'm going to use these Select Next and Previous methods.
回到我的元素定义中
So back in my elements definition,
我要给iron页面一个ID
I'm going to give iron pages an ID,
这样我就可以用Polymer's Automatic Node
and this is just so I can select it more easily using
来更方便地选择 而且我就不用做查询选取
Polymer's Automatic Node finding so I don't have to do query
之类的工作了
select or anything like that.
我给它命名Pages
And I just called it Pages.
在go prev里 我可以输入这个
And now inside of go prev, I can say this,
.$ pages来把那个元素定为目标
.$ pages to target that element,
然后输入Select Previous
and call Select Previous
然后继续
and then go next.
我会做相同的事 但是这次我会
I will do the same thing but, this time, I'll
输入选择下一页
call Select Next.
那么现在我可以切换回Chrome
So now I can switch back to Chrome,
我设好了下一页和前一页选项
and I've got my Next and Previous buttons
还有类似猫录图像圆盘传送带的东西
and our sort of cat-alogue image carousel type thing
现在完善了更多 我们可以翻看
is now a bit more interactive and we can flip through
这些漂亮的猫咪图片了
all these beautiful cat photos.
现在我想做的下一件事是将那个小文本
Now, the next thing I want to do is add that little text input
加在中间 那我就可以知道我正在
in the middle, so I can see which cat
看哪张猫咪图片了
photo I'm currently viewing.
为了做到那样 我要回到我的元素定义
To do that, I will go back to my element definition,
之后我只是放一个普通的 以前的输入类型进来
and I'm just going to drop in a regular, old input type
它相当于文本元素
equals text element.
还有这儿有趣的是
And the interesting thing here is
注意我要在它的value里创建一个链接
to note that I'm going to create a binding in its value,
我还要范围变量命名为selected
and I'm going to call my scope variable selected,
那这个名字就是这个被链接的值所共用了
so that will be the shared name for this bound value.
但是注意这里 我也要
But notice here that I'm also going
在输入这个词后面加上冒号
to add two colons after this and type the word input.
那这是在干嘛呢
So what is going on here?
这个嘛 Polymer的数据连接系统
Well, Polymer's data binding system
都是秘密建立在事件上的
is all secretly based on events.
所以当你的元素里有一个属性
So when you have a property in your element,
也许是一个叫age的 举个例子 我们来看看
maybe something called age, for instance-- so let's see.
那么我们有一个叫age的元素 对吧
So we have a property called age, right?
当这个元素改变时 如果你设定它为正确的选项
When this property changes, if you've set it to notify true,
它其实会激发一个叫做age changed事件
it is actually going to fire an event called age changed.
而Polymer会留神这些事件
And Polymer listens for these events
以得知什么时候应该更新它的数据连接
to know when it should update its data bindings.
但是在本地元素的例子中
But in the case of native elements,
当改变的时候它们激发它们自己的事件
they fire their own events when they change.
任何时候它有改变 文本输入元素就会
The text input element fires this input event anytime
激发这个输入事件
it changes,
所以我们需要教会Polymer关于这个事件的东西
and so we need to teach Polymer about this event.
我们要教会它如何操作  我们要
We need to teach it that hey, we want
这个链接是为了只要你得知这个事件
this binding to update whenever you
被激发就会更新
hear this event being fired.
所以我们才要写这个特别句法
So that's what we're doing with this special syntax here,
这是你可以链接到本地HTML元素的方法
and this is how you can bind to native HTML elements.
好的 设好了那个 我可以回到我的iron页面
OK, so with that set up, I can go back up to my iron pages
元素 并且我可以将它的硬编码的
element, and I can replace its hard-coded selected
值换成那个同样的范围变量
value with that same scope variable,
之后我就可以在我的元素给
and then I can just define a property on my element,
定义一个属性
for selected.
我要将其归类为number 我还要给它设一个默认值为0
I'll type it to number, and I'll give it a default value of 0.
那么现在 如果我们想预览这东西的话
So now, if we go ahead and preview this thing,
我们有一个0值在下面
we've got that 0 value down there,
而且你可以看见当我们点击后一页和前一页时它会改变
and you can see it's changing as we click Next and Previous.
我们也可以点击输入文本
We can also type in the text input,
因为它在激发那个输入事件
and because it's firing that input event,
我们知道一旦改变就会
we know to update our bindings when
更新我们的链接
that changes there as well.
现在 我想做的一件事是
Now, one of things I want to do is
改进一下那些控制布局 还有 Polymer0.5
make those controls lay out a bit nicer and, in Polymer 0.5,
我们总是谈论布局属性
we always talked about layout attributes.
我在我做的每次展示都用
I used them in every demo I ever did.
在Polymer1.0 那些已经被
In Polymer 1.0, those have now been
移到它们自己的repo 叫做Iron Flex Layout
moved to their own repo that is called Iron Flex Layout.
我要引入Iron FLex Layout
I'm going to import Iron Flex Layout,
你可以看见这里有一条我正在用的
and you can see here it's got a special path
特殊路径
that I'm using here.
那么是iron flex layout/classes/iron flex
So it's iron flex layout/classes/iron flex
layout.html.
其实这可以加载一些我能在伸缩编辑上
And that's actually going to load a bunch of CSS classes
用的CSS类
that I can use for Flexbox.
那我们已经从属性转换到类了
So we've switched from attributes to classes now,
但它跟Polymer0.5
but it's basically the exact same thing from Polymer 0.5
基本是一样的
land.
这些事你知道的并喜爱的Flexbox捷径
It's all the Flexbox shortcuts that you know and love.
所以在我的controls div我要添加
So on my controls div, I will add
布局 水平的 可选择的 现在
layout, horizontal and justified, and now
这个布局就很好了 而且我们仍然可以
these guys layout really nice, and we can still
在照片之间切换
toggle through them.
所以这个超级有用
So this is just super useful.
我知道很多人在疑惑
I know a lot of folks were wondering
布局属性去哪了 原来在这
where layout attributes went, so that is where they are.
它们现在到Iron Flex Layout了
They're off in Iron Flex Layout now.
而且对于每一个元素 如果你想用那些类的话
And, for every element, if you want to use those classes,
你需要引入它们 以使它们
you'll need to import them so that they
在范围内工作
work within that scope.
所以很重要 需要注意
So important thing to note there.
现在 我想展示的最后一件事是
Now, the last thing I want to show off
Polymer0.5中很受欢迎的一个特征
is a feature that was very popular in Polymer 0.5, which
人们有时候不想有
was sometimes people didn't want to have
一个数值的selected索引
a numeric selected index.
所以他们会用这个特殊的属性
So they would use this special property
或者这个特殊的属性 叫做值加法器,值属性
or the special attribute called value adder, value attribute.
它可以把那添加到他们的core页面元素
They would add that to their core pages element,
它们之后还会在所有
and they would then specify an attribute
当你尝试更新这东西时你该找的分区
on all of their sections that you should look for when you're
指定一个属性
trying to update this thing.
这在Polymer1.0中被iron页面所替换
This has been replaced in Polymer 1.0 with iron pages.
现在叫做可供选择的加法器
Is now called adder for selected.
那么我们要这个代替老的值加法器
So we're going to use this instead of the old value adder
来输入我们要创建一个叫做猫
to say that we're going to create an attribute called data
的属性 这个属性就是编制的
cat, and this is just a made-up attribute.
我要将它添加到我所有的分区
I'm going to add it to all of my sections,
我还要给它一个值来代表
and I'm going to give it a value that sort of typifies
分区里的东西
what is in that section.
那么这个 由于这是只漂亮的猫咪
So this, since it's a pretty cat,
它的猫的值就很适合
its data cat value is pretty.
这是只度假猫咪 所以这是度假猫
This is a vacation cat, so it's vacation.
黑客猫咪就是黑客猫了
Hacker cat gets hacker.
现在 就下来要发生的是 当那个被选择的值
Now, what's going to happen is when that selected value
改变为字符串时 iron页面
changes to some string, iron pages
会浏览这些不同的分区
is going to look through these different sections.
那我们假设字符串是黑客
And let's say the string is hacker.
它就会浏览这些不同分区
It's going to look through the different sections
像是在问谁有一只匹配的黑客猫呀
and be like who has a matching hacker data cat?
啊 是这里这只啊
Ah, this guy, right here.
之后它会使这个成为被选择的项
And it's going to make this the selected item.
所以如果我到下面直接将我的被选择属性
So if I go down and I just change my selected property
自动改为 默认是黑客猫
to a string and default it to hacker,
现在当我们预览时 你会看见
now when we go in preview, you'll
文本输入是黑客
see that the text input has hacker,
而且当我们浏览不同分区时
and as we're flipping through the different sections,
它会改成我们的不同的猫咪数据值
it changes to our different data cat values.
我们在这里可以输入一个新的
And we can type in a new one here.
它会消失一下
It's going to disappear for a second
因为它像是要变一下空值 但我们可以输入新的
because it sort of goes null for a bit, but we can type in new ones
并看见那些不同的猫咪
and see those different cats as well.
就是这些了
So there you have it.
简洁明了 有着一些小小的更新
Nice and simple, and with some pretty small updates,
我们又可以正常运作了
we're up and running again.
正如你们看到的 这就是本周的内容
That's it for this week, folks.
要记得点那个小小的订阅按钮哦
Be sure to click that little subscribe button.
如果你有问题要问我 发送在
If you have questions for me, leave them
下面的评论区
down in the comments below.
一如既往 我们感谢您的收看
As always, thank you so much for watching,
我们下次再见
and I'll see you next time.
[MUSIC PLAYING]